Guide to the Rice University scrolls representing Chairs, Scholarships, Lectureships, 1918-2013 UA 321
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University scrolls representing Chairs, Scholarships, Lectureships
1918-2013
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 321
3 Linear Feet 3 boxes
Rice University paper scrolls representing and describing gifts to Rice the establishment of Chairs, Scholarships, Lectureships, 1918-2013.
Biographical / Historical
Academic life at Rice University is supported by generous donations to the university. In some cases, such gifts are made to support chairs, scholarships and lectureships. Printed scrolls are created to publicly recognize donors or the persons for whom the donations were made.
Scope and Contents
Rice University paper scrolls representing and describing gifts to Rice the establishment of Chairs, Scholarships, Lectureships, 1918-2013.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from the Development Office, Rice University.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges; Education
Document Types
certificates
- Series I: Scrolls dated 1918-1979
  - 6-1918; Graham BAKER Studentship [2] (Box 1)
  - 6-1918; HOHENTHAL Scholarship Fund [3] (Box 1)
  - 6-1918; SHARP Lectureship [4] (Box 1)
  - 12-1919; GODWIN Lectureship (Box 1)
  - 6-1922; Music Lectureship [2] (Box 1)
  - 6-1932; Samuel Fain CARTER Fellowship [2] (Box 1)
  - 7-1935; CHAPMAN-BRYAN Memorial Scholarship (Box 1)
  - 3-25-1952; Harry Carothers WIESS Chair of Geology [2] (Box 1)
  - 4-23-1953; Harris MASTERSON, Jr. Chair in History [3] (Box 1)
  - 4-1953; Harris MASTERSON Jr. Chair in History, holder Alida C. Metcalf [2014] (Box 1)
  - 10-1958; Reginald Henry HARGROVE Chair of Economics [2] (Box 1)
  - 10-1958; Reginald Henry HARGROVE Chair of Economics, holder Robin Christopher Sickles ([3] (Box 1)
  - 5-1962; Thomas Cooke and Mary Elizabeth EDWARDS Memorial Fund [2] (Box 1)
  - 5-1962; Thomas Cooke and Mary Elizabeth EDWARDS Memorial Fund, holder Keith E. Hamm (Box 1)
  - 6-5-1962; Robert A. WELCH Chair in Chemistry [3] (Box 1)
  - 10-1962; Henry S. FOX, Sr. Chair (Box 1)
  - 10-1962; Gladys Louise FOX Chair (Box 1)
  - 10-1962; William Gaines TWYMAN Chair (Box 1)
  - 3-1963; J. Newton RAYZOR Chair in Philosophy and Religious Thought [3] (Box 1)
  - 4-1964; Libbie Shearn MOODY Professorship in English [2] (Box 1)
  - 4-1964; W.L. MOODY, Jr. Professorship of Mathematics [2] (Box 1)
  - 7-1965; Albert THOMAS Chair of Political Science [4] (Box 1)
  - 7-1965; Albert THOMAS Chair of Political Science, holder Brett Ashley Leeds (Box 1)
  - 7-1965; Albert THOMAS Chair of Political Science, holder Richard J. Stoll (Box 1)
  - 12-1965; Isabel C. CAMERON Chair in Engineering, holder Jennifer L. West (Box 1)
  - 6-1966; Jesse H. JONES Professorship in Management [3] (Box 1)
  - 6-1966; Mary Gibbs JONES Professorship in History [2] (Box 1)
  - 6-1966; Mary Gibbs JONES Professorship in Humanities, holder Edward Snow (Box 1)
  - 9-1966; Edgar Odell LOVETT Professorship in Mathematics [3] (Box 1)
  - 9-1966; Edgar Odell LOVETT Professorship in Mathematics, holder Alexander I. Bufetov (Box 1)
  - 5-1967; William Pettus HOBBY Chair in American History [3] (Box 1)
  - 7-1967; Louis CALDER Professorship in Chemical Engineering [3] (Box 1)
  - 7-1967; Louis CALDER Professor of Chemical Engineering, holder Antonios G. Mikos [3] (Box 1)
  - 3-1968; FAVROT Professorship in French [3] (Box 1)
  - 5-1969; Harry K. and Albert K. SMITH Chair in Architecture [3] (Box 1)
  - 5-1969; Carolyn and Fred MCMANIS Professorship in Philosophy [2] (Box 1)
  - 10-1969; Allyn R. and Gladys M. CLINE Professorship in Economics and Finance [2] (Box 1)
  - 10-1969; Allyn R. and Gladys M. CLINE Professorship in Economics, holder George R. Zodrow [2] (Box 1)
  - 10-1969; Allyn R. and Gladys M. CLINE Professorship in Sociology, holder Steve H. Murdock [2] (Box 1)
  - 10-1969; Allyn R. and Gladys M. CLINE Professorship in Sociology, holder Michael O. Emerson (Box 1)
  - 11-1969; Agnes Cullen ARNOLD Professorship in Fine Arts [2] (Box 1)
  - 11-1969; Agnes Cullen ARNOLD Professorship (Box 1)
  - 11-1969; Agnes Cullen ARNOLD Professorship, holder Anthony Bernard Pinn (Box 1)
  - 11-1969; J. Newton RAYZOR Chair in Philosophy and Religious Thought, holder Jeffrey J. Kripal (Box 1)
  - 10-1970; Harmon WHITTINGTON Professorship [3] (Box 1)
  - 1-1971; Distinguished Professorship of Architecture [2] (Box 1)
  - 1-1971; Gus Sessions WORTHAM Professorship in Architecture, holder David Morrow Guthrie (Box 1)
  - 7-1971; Henry Gardiner SYMONDS Professorship [4] (Box 1)
  - 12-1972; E. D. BUTCHER Professorship at Rice University [2] (Box 1)
  - 12-1972; E. D. BUTCHER Professorship at Rice University, holder Vivek Sarkar (Box 1)
  - 12-1972; E. D. BUTCHER Professorship at Rice University, holder Seiichi P.T. Matsuda (Box 1)
  - 12-1972; E. D. BUTCHER Professorship at Rice University, holder Ka-Yiu San (Box 1)
  - 4-1973 A. J. HARTSOOK Chair in Chemical Engineering [2] (Box 1)
  - 12-21-1973; Andrew W. MELLON Professorship in the Humanities [2] (Box 1)
  - 12-21-1973; Andrew W. MELLON Distinguished Chair of English, holder Jane Chance [2] (Box 1)
  - 12-21-1973; Andrew W. MELLON Professorship in the Humanities, holder Harvey E. Yunis (Box 1)
  - 1-1974; Herman and George R. BROWN Professorship in Civil Engineering [3] (Box 1)
  - 1-1974; Noah HARDING Professorship in Mathematics [2] (Box 1)
  - 1-1974 Noah HARDING Professorship in Computational and Applied Mathematics, holder Professor Emeritus Robert E. Bixby (Box 1)
  - 1-1974; Noah HARDING Professorship in Computational and Applied Mathematics, holder Dan Sorensen (Box 1)
  - 1-1974; Noah HARDING Professorship in Computational and Applied Mathematics, holder Liliana Borcea (Box 1)
  - 1-1974; Andrew Hays BUCHANAN Professorship in Astrophysics [2] (Box 1)
  - 1-1974 George R. BROWN Professorship in Civil Engineering, holder Pedro Jose Alvarez (Box 1)
  - 1-1974; Noah HARDING Professorship in Computational Science and Bioengineering, holder Lydia E. Kavraki (Box 1)
  - 6-1975; J. S. ABERCROMBIE Chair in the School of Engineering [2] (Box 1)
  - 6-1975; J. S. ABERCROMBIE Chair in the School of Engineering, holder Don Johnson (Box 1)
  - 6-1975; Carey CRONEIS Chair in Geology [2] (Box 1)
  - 6-1975; Karen Ostrum GEORGE Chair in Computational Engineering, holder Moshe Y. Vardi (Box 1)
  - 6-1975; Noah HARDING Professorship in Computational and Applied Mathematics, holder James Thompson (Box 1)
  - 6-1975; Noah HARDING Professorship in Computational and Applied Mathematics, holder William Symes (Box 1)
  - 6-1975; Karl F. HASSELMAN Chair in Engineering, holder Willy Zwaenenpoel (Box 1)
  - 6-1975; Lee Hage JAMAIL Chair in Latin American Studies, holder Beatriz Gonzales-Stephan (Box 1)
  - 6-1975; Charles W. DUNCAN, Jr. Welch Chair in Chemistry, holder Andrew Barron (Box 1)
  - 6-1975; William Ward WATKIN Endowed Chair in Architecture, holder Lars Lerup (Box 1)
  - 6-1975; Class of 1921 Scholarship Fund [2] (Box 1)
  - 6-1975; Karl F. HASSELMANN Chair in Engineering, holder Ariel Fernandez (Box 1)
  - 12-1975; Harry S. CAMERON Chair in Mechanical Engineering [2] (Box 1)
  - 2-1976; Harry and Hazel CHAVANNE Chair of Religious Studies [2] (Box 1)
  - 2-1976; Harry and Hazel CHAVANNE Chair in Christian Theology, holder Elias Kifou Bongmba [3] (Box 1)
  - 6-1976; W. Maurice EWING Professorship in Oceanography [3] (Box 1)
  - 12-1976; George PETERKIN Chair of Political Economy (Box 1)
  - 12-1976; [Radoslav] TSANOFF Chair of Public Affairs (Box 1)
  - 12-1976; Radoslav TSANOFF Chair in Public Affairs, holder Lyn Ragsdale (Box 1)
  - 12-1976 [1977]; Isla Carroll and Percy E. TURNER Chair for Biblical Studies, holder April D. Deconick (Box 1)
  - 12-1977; Isla Carroll and Percy E. TURNER Chair for Biblical Studies (Box 1)
  - 12-1977; Herbert S. AUTREY Chair in Social Sciences, holder Stephen J. Motowidlo (Box 1)
  - 3-1978; Joseph and Joanna Nazro MULLEN Professorship in Fine Arts [3] (Box 1)
  - 3-1978; William Alexander KIRKLAND Professorship in Administration [3] (Box 1)
  - 3-1978; William Alexander KIRKLAND Professorship in Administration [3] (Box 1)
  - 3-1978; Martha and Henry Malcolm LOVETT Distinguished Service Chair, holder Marcia J. Citron (Box 1)
  - 3-1978; Joseph and Ida Kirkland MULLEN Professorship in Music, holder Leone Buyse (Box 1)
  - 5-1978; Herbert S. AUTREY Chair in Administration [4] (Box 1)
  - 12-1978; Herbert S. AUTREY Chair in Social Sciences [2] (Box 1)
  - 12-1978; Lynette S. AUTREY Chair in Humanities [2] (Box 1)
  - 9-1979; Stanley C. MOORE Chair in Bioengineering, holder Rebecca Rae Richards-Kortum (Box 1)
  - 11-1979; Stanley C. MOORE Chair in Engineering [3] (Box 1)
- Series II: Scrolls dated 1980-1999
  - 1-1980; George R. BROWN Chair in Administration [2] (Box 2)
  - 1-1980; George R. BROWN Professor of Strategic Management, holder Robert Hoskisson (Box 2)
  - 10-1980; SCHLUMBERGER Chair of Advanced Studies and Research (Box 2)
  - 10-1980; SCHLUMBERGER Chair of Advanced Studies and Research, holder Daniel D. Carson (Box 2)
  - 3-1981; Sam and Helen WORDEN Chair in Physics (Box 2)
  - 3-1981; Sam and Helen WORDEN Chair in Physics, holder Barry Dunning (Box 2)
  - 8-1981; D. R. BULLARD-WELCH Foundation Chair in Science (Box 2)
  - 1-1982; Lynette S. AUTREY Chair in Humanities designated for the Shepherd School of Music (Box 2)
  - 1-1982; Lynette S. AUTREY Chair in Religious Studies, holder Jeffrey J. Kripal (Box 2)
  - 3-1982; Norman and Gene HACKERMAN Chair in Chemistry (Box 2)
  - 3-1982; Norman and Gene HACKERMAN Assistant Professor in Chemistry, holder Eugene R. Zubarev [3] (Box 2)
  - 5-1982; Herbert S. AUTREY Chair in Social Sciences (Box 2)
  - 3-1983; Lynette S. AUTREY Chair in Management [2] (Box 2)
  - 4-1983; Nina J. CULLINAN Chair in Art and Art History, holder Joseph Manca [2] (Box 2)
  - 6-1983; Ralph and Dorothy LOONEY Chair in Biochemistry (Box 2)
  - 6-1983; Ralph and Dorothy LOONEY Chair in Biochemistry, holder Bonnie Bartel (Box 2)
  - 8-1983; Craig Francis CULLINAN Chair (Box 2)
    - 9-1983; Herbert S. AUTREY Chair in Humanities (Box 2)
  - 12-1983; W. M. KECK Foundation Professorship in Geophysics (Box 2)
  - 9-1984; Elma SCHNEIDER Chair in Humanities designated for the Shepherd School of Music (Box 2)
  - 11-13-1984; FOYT Family Chair in Engineering [2] (Box 2)
  - 12-1984; Dorothy Richard STARLING Chair in Classical Violin (Box 2)
  - 5-1986; E. D. BUTCHER Professorship [2] (Box 2)
  - 5-1986; E. D. BUTCHER Chair in Biochemistry and Cell Biology at Rice University, holder George N. Bennett (Box 2)
  - 9-1986; Samuel G. MCCANN Chair in History (Box 2)
  - 9-1986; Lewis B. RYON Chair in Engineering [2] (Box 2)
  - 5-1987; Milton B. PORTER Chair in Mathematics (Box 2)
  - 5-1988; H. Joe NELSON, III Chair in the Jesse H. Jones Graduate School o Administration [2] (Box 2)
  - 5-1988; H. Joe NELSON, III Chair in the Jesse H. Jones Graduate School of Administration, holder William H. Glick (Box 2)
  - 12-1988; John W. COX Chair in Biochemical and Genetic Engineering [3] (Box 2)
  - 1-1989; Lynette S. AUTREY Chair in Social Science, holder James L. Dannemiller (Box 2)
  - 3-1989; [Second] Lynette S. AUTREY Chair in Humanities (Box 2)
  - 3-1989; Herbert S. AUTREY Chair in Social Sciences [3] (Box 2)
  - 10-1989; Harry Carothers and Olga Keith WIESS Chair in Natural Sciences, holder Qimiao Si (Box 2)
  - 10-1989; Harry Carothers and Olga Keith WIESS Chair in Natural Sciences, holder Joan E. Strassman (Box 2)
  - 10-1989; Harry Carothers and Olga Keith WIESS Chair in Natural Sciences, holder David C. Queller (Box 2)
  - 6-1991; Anna Smith FINE Chair in Judaic Studies [3] (Box 2)
  - 7-1991; J. Howard CREEKMORE Chair in the Jesse H. Jones Graduate School of Administration [3] (Box 2)
  - 7-1991; Houston Endowment Professor of Finance, holder Jeff Fleming (Box 2)
  - 7-1991; Houston Endowment Professor of Management, holder Jing Zhou (Box 2)
  - 7-1991; J. Howard CREEKMORE Professor Management, holder Kerry E. Back (Box 2)
  - 7-1991; Houston Endowment Professor of Accounting, holder Thomas Hemmer (Box 2)
  - 3-1992; Gene C. and Norman HACKERMAN Chair in Chemistry [2] (Box 2)
  - 6-1992; Karl F. HASSELMANN Chair in Engineering [2] (Box 2)
  - 6-1992; Karl F. HASSELMANN Chair in Engineering, holder Kyriacos A. Athanasiou [2] (Box 2)
  - 10-1993; Aron and Anaruth GORDON Institute Fellow in the James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy [2] (Box 2)
  - 5-1994; Clarence L. CARTER Chair in Legal Studies [2] (Box 2)
  - 5-1994; Janice and Robert MCNAIR Chair in Public Policy [2] (Box 2)
  - 5-1994; Clarence L. CARTER Chair (Box 2)
  - 5-1994; Clarence L. CARTER Chair, holder Paul Brace (Box 2)
  - 6-1994; FRIEDKIN Chair in Management [2] (Box 2)
  - 6-1994; FRIEDKIN Chair in Management, holder G. Anthony Gorry (Box 2)
  - 6-1994; Martha and Henry Malcolm LOVETT Distinguished Service Professor, holder Marcia Citron (Box 2)
  - 11-1994; William W. AKERS Chair in Chemical Engineering [2] (Box 2)
  - 11-1994; William W. AKERS Chair in Chemical Engineering, holder Ramon Gonzalez (Box 2)
  - 11-1994; William W. AKERS Chair in Chemical Engineering, holder Walter G. Chapman (Box 2)
  - 12-1994; Bonner Means BAKER Fellow in the James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy [2] (Box 2)
  - 2-1995; L. John and Ann. H. DOERR Endowed Chair in Computational Engineering (Box 2)
  - 2-1995; L. John and Ann H. DOERR Endowed Chair in Computational Engineering, holder Ken Kennedy (Box 2)
  - 5-1995; Arab-American Educational Foundation Chair in Arab Studies [2] (Box 2)
  - 5-1995; MAXFIELD AND OSHMAN Professorship in Engineering [2] (Box 2)
  - 5-1995; MAXFIELD AND OSHMAN Professorship in Engineering, holder Richard A. Tapia (Box 2)
  - 5-1995; Janice and Robert MCNAIR Chair in Public Policy [2] (Box 2)
  - 7-1995; Diana Tamari SABBAGH Foundation Fellow in Middle Eastern and Central Asian Affairs [2] (Box 2)
  - 8-1995; Arab-American Educational Foundation Chair in Arab Studies, holder Ussama Makdisi (Box 2)
  - 12-1995; Harry and Hazel CHAVANNE Chair in Religion and Public Policy and Senior Scholar in the James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy [2] (Box 2)
  - 12-1995; Texas Instruments Visiting Professorship [2] (Box 2)
  - 12-1995; Charles W. DUNCAN, JR.-WELCH Chair in Chemistry [3] (Box 2)
  - 1-1996; James Foulds BARBOUR Chair in Mechanical Engineering [2] (Box 2)
  - 2-1996; Isaac and Mildred BROCHSTEIN Fellow in Peace and Security in Honor of Yitzhak Rabin [2] (Box 2)
  - 10-1996; BAKER BOTTS Fellow in the Baker Institute [2] (Box 2)
  - 11-1996; Karen Ostrum GEORGE Chair in Computational Engineering [2] (Box 2)
  - 12-1996; STEWART Memorial Chair [2] (Box 2)
  - 1-1997; Kuwait Foundation Fellow in the Baker Institute [2] (Box 2)
  - 4-1997; J. Hugh LIEDTKE Chair in Management (Box 2)
  - 7-1997; Benjamin and Mary Greenwood ANDERSON Chair in Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science [2] (Box 2)
  - 7-1997; Benjamin M. and Mary Greenwood ANDERSON Chair in Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, holder Pulickel M. Ajayan (Box 2)
  - 8-1997; The Chair in Islamic Economics, Finance and Management (Box 2)
  - 12-1997; T. T. and W. F. CHAO Chair in Chemistry [3] (Box 2)
  - 12-1997; Ervin Kenneth ZINGLER Chair in Economics [3] (Box 2)
  - 1-21-1998; Amoco Corporation recognition (Box 2)
  - 2-25-1998; IBM Corporation recognition (Box 2)
  - 4-1998; [second] J. Hugh LIEDTKE Chair in Management [2] (Box 2)
  - 4-1998; J. Hugh LIEDTKE Chair in Management, holder Vikas Mittal (Box 2)
  - 5-1998; Fayez SAROFIM Chair in Science and Engineering, holder Randall Hulet (Box 2)
  - 5-1998; [second] Isaac and Mildred BROCHSTEIN Fellow in Peace and Security In honor of Yitzhak Rabin (Box 2)
  - 9-24-1998; Intel Corporation recognition (Box 2)
  - 10-1998; Lee Hage JAMAIL Chair in Latin American Studies [2] (Box 2)
  - 10-1998; Joseph D. JAMAIL Chair in Latin American Studies [2] (Box 2)
  - 10-1998; Joseph D. JAMAIL Chair in Latin American Studies, holder Mark Penfield Jones (Box 2)
  - 11-1998; Baker Institute Senior Fellow in Health Policy [2] (Box 2)
  - 12-1998; Taylor and Robert H. RAY Faculty Chair in the Baker Institute [2] (Box 2)
  - 12-1998; The Sid W. RICHARDSON and Taylor and Robert H. RAY Faculty Fellowship in Health Policy [2] (Folder 2)
  - 7-1998; Mary Gibbs JONES Chair in the Jesse H. Jones Graduate School of Management (Box 2)
  - 1-1999; M. D. ANDERSON Foundation Scholar in the Baker Institute [2] (Box 2)
  - 1-1999; James H. and Deborah T. GODWIN Professor of Natural Sciences (Box 2)
  - 1-1999; James H. and Deborah T. GODWIN Professor of Natural Sciences, holder Jennifer Anne Rudgers (Box 2)
  - 3-1999; Martha and Henry Malcolm LOVETT Distinguished Service Chair [2] (Box 2)
  - 4-1999; Bruce and Elizabeth DUNLEVIE Chair in English [3] (Box 2)
  - 5-1999; William Ward WATKIN Endowed Chair in Architecture [2] (Box 2)
  - 7-1999; Mary Gibbs JONES Chair in the Jesse H. Jones Graduate School of Management [2] (Box 2)
- Series III: Scrolls dated 2000-2013 and undated
  - 3-2000; Watt J. and Lilly G. JACKSON Professorship in Biblical Studies (Box 3)
  - 3-2000; Watt J. and Lilly G. JACKSON Professorship in Biblical Studies, holder Matthias Henze (Box 3)
  - 5-2000; Wallace S. WILSON Research Fellow in Energy Studies in the James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy [2] (Box 3)
  - 8-2000; Howard R. HUGHES, Jr. Chair for the Provost of Rice University [3] (Box 3)
  - 8-2000; Howard R. HUGHES, Jr. Chair for the Provost of Rice University, holder Eugene Levy [2] (Box 3)
  - 11-2000; LAY family Chair (Box 3)
  - 11-2000; LAY family Chair, holder Simon H. Grant (Box 3)
  - 2000; David Auston recognition (Box 3)
  - 1-2001; John Antony WEIR Chair in History [3] (Box 3)
  - 11-2001; William and Stephanie SICK Professorship in Entrepreneurship (Box 3)
  - 11-2001; William and Stephanie SICK Professorship in Entrepreneurship, holder Sallie Keller-McNulty (Box 3)
  - 11-2001; Gerald D. HINES Chair in Real Estate Finance (Box 3)
  - 11-2001; Gerald D. HINES Chair in Real Estate Finance, holder Christopher T. Downing (Box 3)
  - 6-2002; George and Cynthia MITCHELL Chair in Sustainable Development (Box 3)
  - 6-2002; George and Cynthia MITCHELL Chair in Sustainable Development, holder Peter Reginald Hartley (Box 3)
  - 6-2002; Jesse H. Jones Graduate School of Administration Acknowledgment of Generous Alumni (Box 3)
  - 6-2002; Class of 1952 Golden Anniversary Scholarship Endowment (Box 3)
  - 9-2002; Kenneth S. PITZER-SCHLUMBERGER Chair (Box 3)
  - 9-2002; Kenneth S. PITZER-SCHLUMBERGER Chair, holder Vicki L. Colvin [3] (Box 3)
  - 9-2003; Walter Kris HUBERT Chair in Music (Box 3)
  - 9-2003; Walter Kris HUBERT Chair in Music, holder Larry Rachleff (Box 3)
  - 10-2003; Frances Moody NEWMAN Professorship in Humanities (Box 3)
  - 4-2004; Malcolm GILLIS University Professorship ([2] (Box 3)
  - 4-2004; Malcolm GILLIS University Professorship, holder Neal Lane (Box 3)
  - 9-2004; Victor E. CAMERON Chair In Engineering [2] (Box 3)
  - 9-2004; Victor E. CAMERON Chair in Engineering, holder Richard G. Baraniuk (Box 3)
  - 12-2004; Verne F. SIMONS Distinguished Professorship in Business [2] (Box 3)
  - 12-2004; William S. MACKEY, Jr. Distinguished Professorship in Business [2] (Box 3)
  - 2004; Class of 1954 Golden Anniversary Scholarship (Box 3)
  - 3-2005; Grace Christian VIETTI Professor of Visual Arts (Box 3)
  - 5-25-2005; E. William Barnett and Margaret Barnett recognition (Box 3)
  - 5-25-2005; Constance J. Burke recognition (Box 3)
  - 6-2005; Class of 1955 Golden Anniversary Scholarship (Box 3)
  - 6-16-2005; Woodson Courtyard [2] (Box 3)
  - 6-24-2005; Gilbert and Ruth WHITAKER Business Information Center (Box 3)
  - 11-2005; William and Stephanie SICK Dean of Engineering (Box 3)
  - 11-2005; William and Stephanie SICK Dean of Engineering, holder Sallie Keller-McNulty (Box 3)
  - 2006; Class of 1956 Golden Anniversary Scholarship (Box 3)
  - 1-2007; Ken and Audrey KENNEDY Chair [2] (Box 3)
  - 1-2007; Ken and Audrey KENNEDY Chair, holder Krishna V. Palem [2] (Box 3)
  - 7-2007; Sheafor-Lindsay Endowment in Engineering (Box 3)
  - 7-2007; Samuel W. and Goldye Marian Spain Faculty Chair in Jewish Studies (Box 3)
  - 11-2007; Linda Faye WILLIAMS Study Room (Box 3)
  - 3-2008; Richard Gilder and Lois Chiles - Barbara Kirkland Chiles Chair in American History (Box 3)
  - 3-2008; Faculty, Staff, and Retirees to the 2012 Faculty and Staff Giving Campaign for Centennial [2 pages] (Box 3)
  - 4-2008; David and Caroline MINTER Chair in the Humanities (Box 3)
  - 4-2008; David and Caroline MINTER Chair in the Humanities, holder Diane Wolfthal (Box 3)
  - 4-2008; Robert Alan and Kathryn Dunlevie HAYES Chair in Humanities (Box 3)
  - 4-2008; William SHAKESPEARE Chair in English (Box 3)
  - 4-2008; SHEAFOR-LINDSAY Chair in Information Technology (Box 3)
  - 5-2008;Louis OWEN Junior Faculty Chair in Engineering (Box 3)
  - 5-2008; Annette and Hugh GRAGG Endowed Chair (Box 3)
  - 6-2008; T. T. and W. F. CHAO Professor of Asian Studies, holder Tani E. Barlow (Box 3)
  - 8-2008; Alan Dugald McKillop Professorship in English [2] (Box 3)
  - 10-2008; Keith T. ANDERSON Professorship in Business [3] (Box 3)
  - 12-2008; DOBELMAN Family Chair [scroll dated XXVII] (Box 3)
  - 1-2009; Barbara Kirkland Chiles Chair in American History (Box 3)
  - 2-2009; John and Ann DOERR Professorship for the Rice Center for Engineering Leadership (Box 3)
  - 2-2009; John and Ann DOERR Professorship for the Rice Center for Engineering Leadership, holder Mark Patrick Embree (Box 3)
  - 3-2009; CARLSON Chair in the School of Humanities (Box 3)
  - 3-2009; CARLSON Chair in the School of Humanities, holder Caroline Levander (Box 3)
  - 7-2009; BROWN-WIESS Professor of Chemistry and Bioengineering, holder John T. McDevitt (Box 3)
  - 11-2009; Rita Shea GUFFEY Chair in English (Box 3)
  - 12-2011; DUNLEVIE Famiy Chair (Box 3)
  - 7-2012; Herbert S. AUTREY Chair in Business (Box 3)
  - 7-2012; Lynette S. AUTREY Chair in Humanities Designated for the Shepherd School of Music (Box 3)
  - 3-2013; 2012 Faculty and Staff Giving Campaign recognition (2 sheets) (Box 3)
  - 8-2013; Alan Dugald McKILLOP Professorship in English (Box 3)
  - 9-2013; Suzanne Deal BOOTH Endowed Chair (Box 3)
  - 4-2015; Ralph S. O'CONNOR Chair in Economics (Box 3)
  - 5-2018 Ralph S. O'CONNOR Chairman's Award (Box 3)
  - 7-2015; SIMONS Chair in Computational and Applied Mathematics and Earth Science [3] (Box 3)
  - 3-2015; Robert L. MOODY Sr. Professorship of Mathematics (Box 3)
  - 9-2015; Suzanne Deal Booth Endowed Chair (Box 3)
  - undated; Endowed Chairs (definition) [2] (Box 3)